we call that regularization when we are
turning or estimates towards some value.
It's zero, for instance.
We see that customer two in red,
it's like confidence interval on zero height
that we will dive here.
And it's not in the same range as we will dive
if we looked only at customer two.
So this model is ready,
but estimating several arcs together
and pulling the estimates.
And what's interesting as well is that at the top you see
we have like a confidence interval
on the third party itself.
And that's in the version modeling.
It's derived from what we call the prior distribution.
And it's just a way to model the third party
on its own and saying,
OK, what's the estimate we have
for the error rate of this third party
given all the data we are observing right now.
And from that we can build another thing system.